えっ 引っ越し
We're going to move?
Two weeks from now?
二週間後に
But...
そんな
What's wrong, Taka? You've
been acting weird these days.
どうしたんだ タカ 最近変だぞ
I need to talk to you about something.
話があるんだ
What is it?
何だ
明日 大事なことを話すから
It's important, but I'll tell you tomorrow.
絶対ここに来てくれ
Make sure you come here.
In that case, I have something really
important to tell you tomorrow too, Taka.
だったら俺も明日 とっても大事なことを鷹に話す
Got it.
分かった
その約束をしたのが引っ越しの二日前のことだった
My news was about moving two days later...
...but...
だけど 翌日日が沈むまで待っても あいつが来ることはなく
...the next day, I waited until the
sun went down, but he never showed.
I left this town without even
saying goodbye to my only friend.
俺は唯一の親友に別れを告げられないまま
この町を去った
A dream?
夢
何で小鳩が
What's with Kobato?
Huh? What was I dreaming about again?
あれ 何の夢見てたっけ
本字幕由诸神卖萌组(kamigami.org)出品 仅供交流学习之用 禁止用于商业用途
---诸神卖萌组---
日听：安少   翻译: 银苹果   校对：喵儿 小草爱吃梨
时间轴：nono   后期：Maize
WANAWANA
Gutto Good hajiketeru
グッと Good 弾ける
Angai nandai hamatten jan
案外なんだい ハマってんじゃん
Hito mishiri shiteru hima ni hajimeyou!
人見知りしてる暇に 始めよう
Tomodachi tsukucchatte asonjatte Yeh!
友達 作っちゃって遊んじゃって Yeah
"Haganai"
Kuuru ni miete, jitsu wa chou sabishii
クールに見えて 実は超寂しい
(Mosou nara bai, bai, bai
Shinyuu nara inai, inai, inai, inai)
妄想ならバイバイバイ
親友なら いないいないいないいない
Nani fujiyuu naku, dakedo tarinai
何不自由なく だけど足りない
(Riajuu kara tooi, tooi, tooi?
Shinyuu nara inai, inai, inai, inai)
リア充から遠い遠い遠い
親友なら いないいないいないいない
Zannen doushi de atsumattara
残念同士で 集まったら
Ah- yosou ga dekinai
Ah- 予想が出来ない 展開の 地雷を踏んだ
Tenkai no jirai wo funda!
SOWASOWA
Zettai, zettai nozokitai
絶対絶対覗きたい
Koukai hyakkai shitakunaitte
後悔100回したくないって
Tsumannai puraido nante
sutekicchatte furikicchatte
つまんない プライドなんて
捨てきっちゃって 振りきっちゃって
Zannen kannen shite mitara,
angai nandai hamatten jan
残念観念してみたら
案外なんだいハマってんじゃん
Butsukatte, dogimagi atte, mitsukeyou!
ぶつかって どぎまぎ合って 見つけよう
Tomodachi tsukucchatte asonjatte Yeh!
友達 作っちゃって遊んじゃって Yeah
Zettai, zettai nozokitai
絶対絶対覗きたい
You! Sutekicchatte furikicchatte
YOU！ 捨てきっちゃって 振りきっちゃって
Yes! Doudai? Doudai, sokontoko
Yes！ どーだいどーだいそこんとこ
"There Aren't Many Customers at the Karaoke Box"
卡拉OK包厢的客人很少
いつの間にか もう一学期が終わってしまったわけだが
The first semester has ended before I knew it...
Yeah, now that you mention it,
summer vacation starts tomorrow.
おお そういや明日から夏休みだもんな
知っての通り 我が隣人部の目的は友達作りだ
As you know, the purpose of the
Neighbors Club is to "make friends."
で この中で友達ができたもの
So, who among us has made any friends?
友達と充実した夏休みを過ごす予定のあるもの
Who among us has plans to spend
a fun-filled summer with friends?
Actually, I think I've got a worse
reputation now than before I joined this club...
つーか 俺は部に入る前より評判が悪化した気がするぞ
Me too. Earlier...
あたしも前に
柏崎さんって 五組のほら あのヤンキーの人と付き合ってるんだって
"I hear Kashiwazaki-san is going
out with that Yankee in class 5!"
...is what I overheard girls
in my class gossiping about.
ってクラスの女子が噂してるの立ち聞きしちゃったわ
I'll get them for that...
あいつら許さない
なんつ か すまん
How can I put it? Sorry...
Y-You don't owe me an apology, Kodaka...
べ 別に小鷹が謝ることじゃないでしょうが
大体皆さん今まで部活ってどんなことをやっていたんですか
What have you done for club activities so far?
Um, what was it?
ええと なんだっけ
確かゲームしたり ゲームしたり
We played video games...
and played video games...
演劇の練習をしたり ゲームしたり
Practiced role-playing...
Played video games...
基本的に遊んでるだけですね
So basically, you just fooled around.
"This is like a real idol concert!"
ね ちょっと聞くけどさ
Hey, let me ask you something...
Have you guys ever been to a karaoke box?
あんたたちカラオケって 行ったことある
Well, yeah, several times
when I was at previous schools.
まあ 前の学校にいった時には何度か
I have, too.
あるぞ
なぜそこまで驚く
Why are you so surprised?
It's hard to imagine you as
someone who does karaoke...
いや あんまりカラオケ行きそうなイメージなかったから
私はこう見えても
I may not look like it, but I've been
to all of the karaoke boxes in the city.
市内のカラオケボックスを全て行き尽くしたくらいのカラオケ通だぞ
That's impressive!
それはすごいな
Going to every single karaoke
box in the city by yourself...
一人で市内のカラオケボックス全制覇とは
Why do you jump to the
conclusion that I was alone?!
なぜ一人だと決めつける
Karaoke boxes are obviously
a place to go with friends!
カラオケボックスは 友達と行くものに決まっているだろう
友達と行くカラオケは楽しいぞ
It's fun singing karaoke with friends!
トモちゃんは歌がうまいだけでなく 聞き上手の盛り上げ上手で
Not only is Tomo-chan a good singer,
she's also a great listener
and keeps the mood merry,
so time always flies by.
いつもあっという間に時間が過ぎてしまう
Right, Tomo-chan. Her air friend.
ああトモちゃんね エア友達の
What's that pitying look for?
なぜそんな憐れむような顔をする
Oh, nothing...
いや 別に
小鷹や夜空ですら行ったことがある何て
Even Kodaka and Yozora have been to one...
Sena, you've never been to a karaoke box?
星奈は行ったことないのか
ないわよ
No...
Want me to apologize?!
悪い 高貴なあたしが
You think a classy girl like myself
カラオケなんて低俗な庶民のお遊びをやったことあるわけないでしょう
would bother with a lowbrow
plebeian pastime like karaoke?!
I'm not interested in it at all!
全然興味もないわ あんなの
中学で誘われなかった時も ちっとも悲しくなかったんだから
And when I never got invited to go in
middle school, I wasn't sad in the least!
All right, got it! Calm down!
分かったから 落ち着けよ
Sempai...
先輩 理科もカラオケ行ったことないです
Rika has never been to a karaoke box either.
前々から興味はあったのですが
Rika's been interested in
going for a long time now...
何分ああいう賑やかな場所に一人で入るのは苦手なもので
...but it's hard entering a
lively place like that all by yourself.
だから 今度ご一緒してくれませんか カラオケ
So next time, how about
going to karaoke together?
Yeah, why not?
ん 別にいいぞ
Thank you!
ありがとうございます
W-Wait, Kodaka! If you want to
go to a karaoke box, leave it to me.
ま…待て小鷹　カラオケのことなら私に任せろ
I know a good place.
いい店を知っている
You'll lead the way? That'll help.
案内してくれるのか そりゃ助かる
あにき
Aniki...
わたくしもカラオケ屋さんには行ったことがありません
I haven't ever been to a karaoke place either.
Now I'm in the mood to
perform "Chaos Requiem," too.
我も久々に混沌のレクイエムを奏でたくなったわ
Okay, when should we go?
じゃあいつにする どうせ明日から夏休みだし
How about tomorrow, our
first day of summer vacation?
私は明日の午後ならいいぞ
I'm free tomorrow afternoon.
Rika can go anytime!
いつでも大丈夫です
わたくしも
Me too.
Then tomorrow it is.
じゃあ明日だな 待ち合わせはどこがいいんだ
Where should we meet?
私の行きつけの店は遠夜西駅から徒歩十分だ
The karaoke box I have in mind is a
ten-minute walk from Tooya Nishi Station.
Then let's meet in front of
the Nishi Station ticket gates.
なら西駅の改札前で待ち合わせで
じゃあ時間は
What time?
ちょ…ちょっと待ってよ
W-Wait a second!
あ…あのね
U-Um...
何だ肉
What is it, Meat?
私たちは今 高貴なお肉様がぜんっぜん興味がなくて
Right now, we're discussing
our plans to go to a karaoke box...
行きたいなんてころっぽちも思っていない
you know, that lowbrow plebeian pastime
カラオケ屋と言う低俗な庶民のお遊びに行く予定について話し合っているのだが
a classy girl like Meat-sama
has absolutely no interest in.
So, Meat, is there something
you're wanting to say?
で肉 なにか話でもあるのか
ないなら私たちは 貴様にはなんの関係もない
If not, this has nothing to do with you.
We want to talk about our plan for tomorrow.
明日の予定の話をしたいのだが
I-I, uh...
あ…あたしは　その
That place's free time starts at 100,
so that's when we'll meet up, all right?
その店のフリータイムが一時からだから
集合時間は午後一時でいいな
昼食は済ませておくこと
Make sure you have lunch beforehand.
Don't ignore me!
無視しないでよ
What is it, Meat?
何だ肉
Don't tell me you want to enjoy a
lowbrow plebeian pastime like karaoke?
まさか貴様も低俗な庶民のお遊びであるカラオケなんかに行きたいとでも言うのか
I-I didn't say I wanted to go...
い…行きたいなんて
Hey, if you want to come with,
you should just be honest and say so.
なぁ 一緒に行きたいなら素直にそう言った方がいいぞ
What? You want to come with us?
何だ 貴様も一緒に行きたいのか
I-I want to...
い…一緒に　い…行きたいわ
...g- go with you guys.
I can't hear you!
聞こえないな
い…一緒にいきたい
I...
I want to go with you!
"Justine, or the Misfortunes of Virtue"
"The Marquis de Sade"
ええ なんだって
What was that?
I wanna go with you guys to sing karaoke!
あたしも一緒にカラオケに行きたい
そうか 貴様の気持ちは分かった
I see. I understand how you feel.
But the thing is, I don't want to go with you.
だが私は貴様と一緒に行きたくないな
どうしても連れて行ってほしいなら
If you really, really want me
to take you, try begging me.
お願いしてみろ
B-Begging?
お…お願い
Put your heart into it and plead,
"Please take me with you."
連れて行ってくださいと 心を込めて頼め
あ…あたしも一緒に　つ…連れて行って　く…ください
P-Please take me w-with y-you...
Huh? I couldn't hear that very well.
おや よく聞こえないな
What about the begging part, Cow Udders?
「お願いします」はどうした 乳牛
- P... le... ase...
- Oh, Yukimura-kun, would you
get Rika another cup of coffee?
おね…ぐぐ…おね…がい…します
ああ幸村くん もう一杯コーヒーいただきますか
かしこまりました
So I can hear you!
もっとはっきりと
Politely, and put your heart into it!
丁寧に 心を込めて
I beg you, please take me with you!
あたしも一緒に連れて行ってください お願いします
よく言えました
Well spoken.
だが断る
But I refuse.
What do I have to do, idiot?!
どうすりゃいいってんのよバカ
明日はあたしも一緒に行くからね
I'm going tomorrow!
て言うかそもそも何で一緒に行くのに夜空の許可がいるのよ
Why would I need your permission
to go in the first place, Yozora?!
You finally figured that out? You really
are lacking in the brains department!
やっと気づいたか 本当に貴様は脳味噌が足りないな
バカ アホ
Stupid!
死ね バカ夜空
Die, stupid Yozora!
では改めて 本当の待ち合わせ場所と時刻を決めようか
Now, why don't we decide
on the real time and place?
Are you a devil?!
鬼かお前は
冗談だ
That was a joke.
明日は一時に約束があるから お昼はいつもより早めにして
I have an appointment tomorrow at 100,
so have lunch prepared earlier than usual.
お約束 お友達とですか
An appointment... with friends?
O-Of course not!
と 友達なわけないわ
単なる部活
It's just with club members.
If I don't go, nothing will happen.
まあ あたしが行かないと始まらないからね
What kind of club activity is it?
どのような活動を
カラオケよ
Karaoke.
あの夜空や小鷹にも あたしの見事な歌声にひれ伏さしてやる
I'm going to ambush Yozora and
Kodaka with my wonderful singing voice!
Ah, I wanna sing a duet with Kobato-chan!
ああ あとは小鳩ちゃんとデュエットしたいかも
Kodaka?
小鷹
遠夜西 遠夜西
Tooya Nishi, Tooya Nishi...
Aren't you hot wearing that?
お前そんな恰好で熱くないのか
ククク 真祖たる我は熱ささえも凌駕しておる
A true heir of the Night
Tribe transcends even heat.
You're not transcending it at all!
全然凌駕できてないだろう
みんないる
Everyone's over there.
Now that we're all here, shall we go?
さて 揃ったし行くか
You guys are all early. It's ten
minutes before the meeting time.
皆早かったな まだ十分前なのに
私は理科より五分遅れて来た
I got here five minutes after Rika.
I arrived twenty minutes before you did, Aniki.
わたくしはあにきが来られた二十分前につきました
理科が来たのは星奈先輩が来た十五分前です
Rika came fifteen minutes before Sena-sempai.
あたしは幸村のつく五分前からいたわ
I was here five minutes
before Yukimura-kun showed up.
Why are you guys talking like it's a math quiz?
何でお前らそんなクイズみたいな言い回しなんだ
小鳩
Kobato, based on what they just said,
みんなの証言からそれぞれの到着時刻を答えてみろ
try to figure out when each of them arrived!
俺たちの到着時刻は十二時五十分ジャストとする
We arrived at exactly 12:50.
You have until we arrive at
the karaoke place to answer.
制限時間は店に着くまで
えっと
Um...
ククク アカシックレコードにアクセスすれば
If I access the Akashic Records,
I'll be able to solve a
problem like this easily.
そのような問題いとも容易く解いてみせよう
Give me a minute.
暫し待っておれ
It's not that big a deal...
そんな大層な問題じゃないけどな
We're not there yet?!
まだ着かないの
Quiet, Meat. We're almost there.
うるさい肉 もうすぐだ
何と言うお店なんですか
What's the name of the karaoke box?
"Cry from the Abyss."
「深淵からのよびごえ」だ
What kind of place is that?
どんなお店ですか
Hey, Taka!
おーい タカ
You're slow, Taka!
遅いよタカ
Wait for me!
待てって
Kodaka! What's wrong?
小鷹 どうした
Bro!
あんちゃん
Yeah...
There!
"Karaoke Box"
"Cry from the Abyss"
いらっしゃいませ
Welcome.
So this is a karaoke box?
ここがカラオケ屋さんですか
フリータイム ドリンクバー
Free time and drink bar!
Um... There are six of you?
ええと 六名様でよろしですか
ああ 六人で
Y-Yes, six...
All right.
かしこまりました
お会計 フリータイムドリンクバー付き六名様
The total for free time
and drink bar for six people...
5400円になります
...is 5,400 yen.
は 5400円
- 5,400 yen?! Why is it that expensive?!
- Brother! Brother!
あんちゃん あんちゃん
なぜそんなに高いのだ
ええと フリータイムお一人様650円 ドリンクバー250円
Um, free time for one person is 650 yen.
The drink bar is 250 yen.
So 900 yen per person...
お一人様計900円となっておりますが
What?!
何だと
Just to confirm, I'll ask again...
念のため訊くが
六人で一部屋なのだな
うちらが到着したのが十二時五十分 あってる あってる
- You mean one room for six people, right?
- We arrived at 12:50! Right?! Am I right?!
- Yeah.
- Wait a second.
- We arrived at 12:50! Right?! Am I right?!
ちょっと待ってくれ
どうしたんだ
What's wrong?
The total doesn't make sense.
料金がおかしい
What do you mean?
どういうこと
ドリンクバーが一人分250円なのはいい
The drink bar for 250 yen a person is fine...
...but why do each of us
have to pay for the room?
だが なぜ部屋代まで一人一人別で計算されているのだ
Is that strange?
何か変なの
Meat, what do you do at a karaoke box?
肉 カラオケボックスとは何をする場所だ
Sing songs, right?
歌を歌う場所じゃないの
Exactly!
その通りだ
一つの部屋で 一人で三十曲歌おうが
In one room, whether
one person sings 30 songs,
or six people sing five songs
each, it's the same 30 songs!
六人で五曲ずつで合計三十曲だろうが 同じ三十曲だ
なのになぜ部屋代を六倍も払わなければならないのだ
So why do we have to pay six
times for the cost of the room?
In other words, it's a scam?
つまり詐欺ってこと
詐欺に近いな
Close to it!
This never happened when
I came here with Tomo-chan.
トモちゃんと二人で来たときは こんなことは一度もなかったのだが
Hold on! You can't count Tomo-chan as a person!
待て待て トモちゃんは一人に数えないだろう
Besides, isn't that how
all karaoke boxes charge?
それに カラオケ屋の料金システムってそういうもんじゃないのか
No, strange is strange.
いや おかしいものはおかしい
This is rare, but I agree with you.
珍しく意見が合ったわね
パパが言ってたわ
Daddy once told me that
the people who stand on top
「上に立つ者は不自然な金の動きを見逃してはならない」って
mustn't overlook the
unnatural movement of money.
I've got it. Why don't we do this?
そうだ だったらこういうのはどう
肉の分際でやるではないか
Not bad for a slab of meat.
さっきは六人と言ったが取り消しだ
Forget what I said about six people.
いつものように フリータイムドリンクバー計900円
As usual, free time and drink bar for 900 yen!
I'm acquainted with those people,
but I'm not here with them.
そこの連中は知り合いだが 連れではなく
We just happened to
come here at the same time.
偶然一緒に入ってしまっただけだ
はい お お一人様900円です
Fine.
That's 900 yen for one person.
Um, this is my first time, but...
ええと 初めてなんだけど
お一人様 フリータイムでドリンクバー付き
Free time and drink bar for one person!
What are they doing?
何のつもりだ
初めてのかたは会員カードをお作りしますので
- Rika supposes the idea is that
we all sing in separate rooms.
- I'll make cards for the first-timers.
全員個室で歌えということなのでしょうか
Then what's the point of
us coming here together?
それじゃ一緒に来た意味ねえじゃねえか
はい じゃあ
Th-That'll be 900 yen...
きゅ 900円になります
小鷹 お前の番だぞ
Kodaka, it's your turn.
We'll go on ahead.
あたしら先に行ってるわよ
H-How many people?
な…何名様ですか
あ 四人で
Um... four.
四名様でよろしいのですか
You're sure, four people?!
Y-Yes...
あ はい
Thank you!
ありがとうございます
It's okay, right?
いいよな
Yes! Let's sing a duet!
はい デュエットしましょう
As long as I can be in the
same room with you, Aniki...
あにきと同じ部屋になるのであれば
ククク 我が美声を聴かせる時が来たようだな
It seems the time has come for
you to hear my beautiful voice.
All right, I'll make a member card for you.
それでは同じく 会員カードをお作りいたします
あ はい
Yeah, sure.
どうかしたのか
Is something wrong?
N-Nothing!
なっ 何でもないわ
That's 3,600 yen.
3600円です
あ はい
Yeah, okay.
へぇ こうなってるんですね
So this is what it looks like...
Wheee!
Please go first, Kodaka-sempai!
ではまず小鷹先輩 いっちゃってください
You want me to start? Let's see...
俺から そうだな
- Orange juice, iced au lait, cola,
and a seaweed drink, please.
- Pump it full of your coolness!
オレンジジュースとアイスオーレとコーラと昆布茶をお願いいたします
格好いいところいっぱしぶっちこんじゃってください
- Orange juice, iced au lait, cola,
and a seaweed drink, please.
- Pump it?
ぶち込むって
あ 黒くて固いのここ置いときますね
I'll put this stiff black thing right here.
Call it a mic!
マイクと言えマイクと
行くか
Guess I'll go...
あにき
Aniki!
時々 もしかしたら何もかも夢なんじゃないかと思うんだ
♪ Sometimes I think that
everything might be a dream. ♪
かつてきみが見たはずの景色の中に僕も今立ってるんだ
♪ The scene I think you once looked at ♪
♪ is where I'm standing now. ♪
♪ I wonder what you were
thinking when you were here. ♪
きみはここで何を思ってたんだろう
きみにしか聞けないことを言いたかったのに
♪ I wanted to ask you something... ♪
"Karaoke Box"
"Cry from the Abyss"
Bro!
あんちゃん
You have a wonderful singing voice, Aniki!
素晴らしい歌声です あにき
Sempai, you have a great voice!
先輩いい声してますね 濡れてしまいそうです
Rika thinks she's going to get wet!
ケケケ 七千年前貴様と共に闇を駆け抜けた時代を思い出す
This makes me recall
running through the moonless
night with you seven years ago...
I have no memory of that.
そんな思い出ねえよ
あ 理科です
It's Rika's turn!
♪ Racing to the crack of dawn... ♪
駆け抜けてよ負けの先まで
"The Way a Man Lives"
- Yukimura?
- ♪ Let's welcome the hour ♪
幸村か
負荷率鈍るとき迎えよう
♪ that the light leads to... ♪
♪ Feel it at an accelerating speed. ♪
加速するスピードで感じて
- ♪ You can leave the consequences to me. ♪
- I wonder if they're singing now, too...
あと先はお任せで さぁ
あいつらも今 歌ってんのかな
...alone...
一人で
どうです 今の「ラブマイクフィニッシュ」
How was that love-mic finish?!
Did you feel a tingle?
ぞくぞくきましたか
Absolutely not!
こねえよ
ええ 昨日徹夜で考えたんですよ
I spent all last night thinking about it!
次はわたくしです この曲をあにきに捧げます
I'm up next.
I dedicate this song to you, Aniki.
I see. Then go for it, Yukimura.
そうか まあ 頑張れ幸村
あいつらの部屋に聞きに行ったら怒られるかな
If I went to their rooms to hear them,
I wonder if they'd be pissed...
They have it! "Go! Go! Guernica-chan!"
あった 「ゆけゆけゲルニカちゃん」
よかったな
Good for you.
♪ When life burns... ♪
命燃やす時
"The Season for Two"
ククク 我が美声を堪能するがよい
Have your fill of my beautiful voice!
"The Season for Two"
窓越し
♪ Through the window, ♪
♪ I was watching your back ♪
歩くきみの背中 ずっと見つめてた
♪ as you walked away. ♪
今より 強くなりそうな雨から目を背けた
♪ I averted my eyes from the rain
that seemed to be pouring stronger ♪
♪ than it is now. ♪
きみが近すぎて気付かなかった
♪ I didn't notice that you were too close. ♪
夢でまた さよならが痛む
♪ That "farewell" I saw in my dream hurts. ♪
今頃分かったよ きみの涙で
♪ Now I understand your tears. ♪
もう二度と会えない
♪ We can never meet again;
I can't keep the promise. ♪
きみを傷つけない 約束もできない
♪ "I won't hurt you." ♪
♪ And there's nothing I can
do to stop you from leaving. ♪
引き留める手は もうない
あ 歌い過ぎて喉が痛い
My throat hurts from singing too much...
Sempai, if you spoke to
Rika with that sadistic voice,
先輩 その声で口汚く罵られたら理科
本格的にMに目覚めちゃいそうです
it might bring out the "M" in her!
Your voice gives me chills, Aniki.
ぞくぞくするお声ですあにき
どうしたんだお前ら
What's wrong with you two?
It's Meat's fault.
この肉が悪い
It's stupid Yozora's fault.
夜空のバカのせいよ
Just how much spirit did
you put into the singing?
どんだけ気合い入れて歌ったんだよ
There's a scoring mode, right?
採点モードってあるじゃない あれやってたのよずっと
I used that the whole time.
It shows the rankings.
ランキングが出るのだ
やり始めたら生意気にも
When I started, impudently enough,
the name "NIGHT" was top-ranked.
上位にNIGHTって名前があって
"Current Rankings"
I figured it was Yozora...
[yozora : night sky]
あ こいつ夜空だって思って
上位を全部私の名前で埋めようとしていたときに
Just when I was trying to fill
up all of the slots with my name,
suddenly the unpleasant name
"SENA" started cutting in...
急にSENAとかいう
見るからに不愉快な文字列が割り込んでくるように
They were in separate
rooms and still fighting?
別の部屋にいてまで喧嘩してる何て
でー勝負はどうなったんですか
So who won?
I did!
私（あたし）
First place was my 99 points!
一位は私の99点だったろうが
That was just by chance!
あんなのまぐれよ
I dominated places 2 through 11
with 98 points across the board!
二位から十一位まであたしの98点が独占してたでしょうが
That means nothing if you don't get first place!
一位を取れなければ意味がない
Besides, I had more 97-point scores than you!
それに97点の数は私の方が上だ
Liar! I had one more 97 score than you!
嘘 97点の数はあたしの方が一つ多かったわ
That's a dirty lie, Meat!
嘘をつくな肉
It's the truth, tone-deaf Yozora!
嘘じゃないわよ音痴夜空
That was fun, wasn't it, Sempai?
Let's come back again sometime.
楽しかったですね先輩 また来ましょう
Yeah...
ありがとうございましたー
Thank you!
これで一学期の部活は終わりでしょうか
So is this our last club
activity for the first semester?
I guess so...
そうだな
So Rika has to wait forty days before
she can fool around with you, Sempai?
42日間も先輩とイチャイチャできなくなっちゃうんですね
Hold it, Rika! Don't talk like
we've been fooling around all this time!
待て理科 これまで俺とイチャイチャしてきたような言い方するな
So I can't be Aniki's gofer for a long time...
あにきのパシリもできなくなるのですか
What the hell are you talking about?!
お前たち一体何を言っている 夏休みも普通に活動するぞ
Even during summer vacation, we're
going to have normal club activities.
えっ 部活やるのか 夏休みも
We're gonna have club
activities even over the summer?
The sports and cultural
clubs will still meet regularly,
運動部も文化部も活動しているのに
so why would we take a vacation?
なぜうちだけが休みなのだ
In the first place, summer is the season
そもそも夏はリア充どもがますます充実する季節だ
when the normal kids have enriching lives.
将来我々がリア充の仲間入りを果たした時
Since our goal is to enter
their ranks in the future,
we need to train in the summer, lest
our hopes for normality die on the vine.
夏の訓練もしておかなければ
あまりのリア充度に死にかれんぞ
It's like the logic of
pouring boiling water in a glass,
ガラスのコップに熱度を入れると 割れてしまうのと同じ理屈ですね
which isn't used to it, so it cracks, right?
Yes, that's right.
ああ その通りだ
That's thermal expansion!
熱膨張だろうそれ
Our next meeting will be next Monday.
次の活動は来週月曜
Each of you think about why you
haven't been able to make any friends
夏休みまでに友達を作れなかった原因を各自考え
- up to summer vacation...
- I know!
What is it, Meat?
なんだ肉
失敗した原因は 夜空が無能すぎるからだと思います
I think the reason for our collective
failure is that Yozora is too incompetent!
Actually, I can think of several causes as well.
実は私もいくつか原因には心当たりがある
One is that you're too stupid, Meat!
それは肉があまりにもバカ過ぎること
Another is that you're really annoying!
肉があまりにうざ過ぎること
低能で無能で
Between your pea-brain and your inability
to do anything, your whole existence
存在自体が部にとって
to the club... no, to the world...
いや 世界にとって
is of no value, and actually a minus!
無価値どころか マイナスにしかならないことなどだ
You'd go that far?!
そこまで言う
Certainly, I said too much.
確かに言い過ぎた
Even though it's impossible to expound fully
貴様がどれだけ世界にとって有害な物質であるかを
on how you're a hazardous
substance to the world,
完璧に説明することなど不可能であったのに
I wasted too many words trying to attempt it.
無駄な言葉を重ねてしまった
バカだの アホだの うざいだの 存在価値がないだの
Like, you're stupid!
いいんですか
- Is it okay to leave them?
- You're an idiot! You're annoying!
You're worthless! You're garbage!
振り向くな
- Don't turn around.
- You're an idiot! You're annoying!
You're worthless! You're garbage!
あにき
- Aniki...
- You're an idiot! You're annoying!
You're worthless! You're garbage!
ゴミだの 蝿以下だの 蛆だの ゴキブリだの うんこだの
- Don't turn around!
- You're lower than a fly!
You're a cockroach! You're poo!
振り向くんじゃない
- Understood.
- You're lower than a fly!
You're a cockroach! You're poo!
分かりました
- Hey... Yozora... people are...
- Even calling you a walking sewage
machine would be a waste of words!
動く汚物製造器だのと言う発言は 本当に無駄にもほどがあったな
夜空…見てる　周り…みんな
...looking...
アホぉ
Idiot!!
Yozora, you idiot! Dumbass! Die! Stupid!
夜空のアホぉ バカ 死ね
アホ夜空ぁぁ
She's hopeless...
毎度毎度しょうがないやつだ
部活が始まってから一か月か
It's been one month since the club started...
こいつからすべてが始まったんだな
It all started with her...
夜空
Yozora!
この一か月 割と楽しかったぞ
This past month has been kind of fun.
ありがとな
Thanks.
小鷹
Kodaka!!
Sena!
星奈
伝え忘れてたわ
I forgot to tell you...
昨日パパに話したら
When I was talking to Daddy yesterday,
「夏休みなら時間取れるから いつでも会いに来なさい」って
he said he has some free time over the
summer, so you can come over anytime.
なんかパパも会いたがってるみたいだったわ
It seems like he wants to meet you, too.
Oh, I see. In that case, I'll visit soon.
そっか それじゃ今度行くよ
来るときはあたしに言ってね
Tell me when you're coming too, okay?
Sure.
W-Wait a second!
ちょ ちょっと待って
何で小鷹が肉の家に行って
Why would Kodaka go to your house, Meat,
そのち…父親に挨拶するのだ
and pay his respects to your f-father?!
Hmm?
いや 俺たちが
Well, we're...
Kodaka!
小鷹
Keep that a secret. It could lead to trouble.
それ秘密にしといて 問題あるかもしれないし
Oh, I see. Okay.
そっか 分かった
確かに
True, it's better not to advertise
「理事長の権限で編入に便利をはかってもらった」なんて
that the president of the school used
his authority to expedite my admission.
大っぴらにしない方がいいか
S-Secret?!
ひ 秘密だと
It has nothing to do with you, Yozora.
別に夜空には何の関係もないことよ
Whether Kodaka comes to
my house or meets my daddy,
小鷹があたしの家に来ようが
あたしのパパに会おうが
it doesn't have a thing to do with you, Yozora.
夜空には全然関係のないことだもんね
じゃあ小鷹 よろしくね
Bye, Kodaka! I'll see you soon!
Yeah.
Aa, nounai souzou risou no genjitsu touhi
あー 脳內 想像理想の 現実逃避
今更どっちだっていっけど 友達作り
Ima sara docchi datte ikkedo... tomodachi zukuri
Hitori sabishii yatsu da to
sagesumu shisen ga ki ni naru
一人寂しい奴だと蔑む 視線が気になる
De, uwattsura dake atsumattara...
で 上っ面だけ集まったら
それでいいと 思っているうちに
Sore de ii to omotte iru uchi ni~
Are yo are yo to toujou, sorotte
あれよあれよと登場 揃って 破天荒な奴らに
Hatenkou na yatsura ni
Maipeesu midasarete yuku
マイペース 乱されてゆく 頭くる！特に憎っくき肉
Atama kuru! Toku ni nikukkuki niku!
Watashi no mune, hisoka
ni asette yuujou fudan kimi de
私の胸秘かに焦って 優柔不斷気味で
My heart tsutaerarenai
My heart 伝えられない 殘念なのは 私なのか
Zannen na no wa watashi na no ka?
Moya moya wo kakiwake Today!
もやもやを かきわけ Today！
Okizari ni sareta otome
gokoro ano hi kara kuyande iru
置き去りにされた 乙女心 あの日から悔やんでいる
Hayaku mitsuke dashite, maigo no kokoro
早く見つけ出して 迷子のココロ
小鷹先輩　よかったですね
Kodaka-sempai! Rika is so happy
we get to see each other over
the summer through the club!
夏休み中も部活で会えますよ
I'm really happy I can meet you too, Aniki!
またお会いできて嬉しいです　あにき
お前らそんなに夏休みにすることないのかよ
Do you two really have that
little to do over summer vacation?
Do you have things to do, Sempai?
先輩にはあるんですか
いや　ないけどさ
Well, no, but...
Rika knew it!
やっぱり
Then over the next forty days,
それじゃこれから40日間理科といっぱいいっぱいHなことしましょうね
let's do all kinds of
perverted stuff with each other!
For the next forty days,
I'll be at your beck and call, Aniki.
40日間パシリをしっかりお務めいたします　あにき
お前らな
Jeez, you two...
次回「携帯電話は着信が少ない」
Next time: " My Cell Phone
Doesn't Get Many Calls."
"Next time: My Cell Phone Doesn't Get Many Calls"
Huh? Aniki's gone.
あれ　あにきがいません
I have no means of contacting Sempai!
先輩に連絡する方法がない